Guide to the Croswell Bowen Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Printed Material, 1919-64; Series IV; 0.5' (1 box)
  - PLAYBILLS
    - New Rochelle Play House, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Théatre Normandie, 1935 Jun 6 (Box 6, Folder 155)
- Oversize
  Oversize material has been placed here in series order.
  - WRITINGS
    - Great River of the Mountain
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 7 (Oversize), Folder 156-66)
    - They Went Wrong
      - Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 7 (Oversize), Folder 167)
    - "Ahab in Seersucker", 1946 Sep 8 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 168)
    - "America's Crime Problem", 1953 Feb 26 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 169)
    - "The Americanization of J. Parnell Thomas", 1947 Nov 30 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 170)
    - "Congress' Bouting Thomas", 1947 Dec 7 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 171)
    - "Dum De Dum Dum", 1954 Feb (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 172)
    - "An Evening with Two Gentlemen", 1948 Jan 18 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 173)
    - "George C. Marshall of Uniontown, PA", 1947 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 174)
    - "The Great Brinks Robbery", 1956 Apr (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 175)
    - "The Great Red Scare of 1920", 1947 Apr 13 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 176)
    - "The Greatest Tragedy of Eugene O'Neill" mixed proofs and galleys, [1959?] May 12 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 177)
    - "Hereinafters and Whereases, Lights, Action, Camera", 1948 Jan 4 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 178)
    - "How Leaders in the Cold War Looked as the Word Barrage Began in the UN", 1947 Sep 21 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 179)
    - "I-Like-Ike for President GHQ Purrs Smooth and Easy as a Rolls Royce", 1947 [Oct] 19 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 180)
    - "'Ladies and Gentlemen, the President of the United States,'", 1948 Mar 21 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 181)
    - "McFeely Meets His Match", 1947 Jun 29 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 182)
    - "A Mourner for the Lonely Spinster Whose Will Is a Suspected Forgery", 1948 Jan 25 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 183)
    - "Night in the Municipal Lodging House", 1947 Dec 14 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 184)
    - "NYC Prepares for UNO", n.d. (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 185)
    - "Sidelong Glance at a Profiler", 1947 Oct 12 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 186)
    - "The Smiling Cop Who Heads the Legion", n.d. (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 187)
    - "Socking Saga of Jersey Joe", 1948 May 9 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 188)
    - "Utopia in the Catskills", 1947 Jul 20 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 189)
    - "Young Man in Quest of Peace", n.d. (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 190)
    - Unidentified, New Yorker, 1955 Sep 10 (Box 8 (Oversize), Folder 191)
    - Scrapbook of clippings, n.d. (Box 9 (Oversize), Folder 192)
    - Scrapbook of clippings from PM's Sunday Picture News (Box 9 (Oversize), Folder 193)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Cartoon by Eric Godal, n.d. (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 194)
    - Photographs
      - Bowen, Croswell, n.d. (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 195)
      - Unidentified statue, n.d. (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 196)
      - Yale Class of '29 Reunion Portrait, 1969
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - The New York Star v.1 no.186, 1949 Jan 28 (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 197)
    - The Daily Compass v. 1 no. 1, May 16, 1949 (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 197)
    - PM v.1 no.1, 1940 Jun 18 (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 198)
    - PM's Picture News, 1944 Oct 29 (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 199)
    - "War in Africa", 1942 Dec 29 (Box 10 (Oversize), Folder 200)